{"data":[{"question":"Most of doctors agree that smoking is bad for your health.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"of","b":"that","c":"smoking","d":"for","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Of->x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"It's a waste of time to try and explain anything with Tony.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"a","b":"to try","c":"anything","d":"with","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- with-> to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Everyone but to Jane failed to produce the correct answer.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Everyone","b":"to","c":"produce","d":"correct","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- To-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Thank you very much for your letter who arrived a few days ago.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"you","b":"for","c":"who","d":"a few","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Who-> which","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"I'm sorry I haven't wrote for such a long time but I've been very busy.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"sorry","b":"wrote","c":"such","d":"been","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Wrote-> written","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"It was in very bad conditional and it needed a lot of work.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"in","b":"conditional","c":"needed","d":"a lot of","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Conditional-> condition","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"We have finished most of the it now and it looks very nice.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"finished","b":"the","c":"and","d":"very","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- The-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Peter and I have decided to give an hour-warming in May 3rd.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"have","b":"to give","c":"hour-warming","d":"in","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- In->on","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Please be give me a ring and let me know if you can make it.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"be","b":"let","c":"know","d":"make","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Be-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"I was reluctant making a promise to buy more goods from the same company.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"reluctant","b":"making","c":"to buy","d":"more","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Making-> to make","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"}]}